in this screencast we're going to look
在本截屏中，我们将看
at how to work with your version control
如何使用版本控制
system inside IntelliJ IDEA for this
IntelliJ IDEA内部的系统为此
example we're going to use git
例子，我们将使用git
IntelliJ IDEA provides completion for
IntelliJ IDEA为完成提供
your github repositories if you're
您的github存储库（如果您是
logged into github via IntelliJ IDEA as
通过IntelliJ IDEA登录到github
usual the completion is smart enough to
通常完成是足够聪明的
recognize sections from the middle of
识别中间的部分
the URL you're looking for in this demo
您在此演示中寻找的URL
I'm going to clone the project to the
我将项目克隆到
default location IntelliJ IDEA
默认位置IntelliJ IDEA
recognizes this is a Gradle project and
意识到这是一个Gradle项目，
automatically uses the Gradle import
自动使用Gradle导入
process to create the new project again
再次创建新项目的过程
we'll use the defaults here this project
我们将在此项目中使用默认值
is imported and built and IntelliJ IDEA
导入并构建，IntelliJ IDEA
automatically understands which of the
自动了解哪个
source and test directories for the
源目录和测试目录
project let's make a small change to see
我们做个小小的改动看看
the version control integration in
中的版本控制集成
action this square class has the methods
这个平方类的动作有方法
sketched out but they have not yet been
勾勒出来，但他们尚未
implemented if we now get to the test
如果我们现在进行测试，则已实施
for this class we can enable the test
对于此类，我们可以启用测试
for the vertices method
用于顶点方法
and run it
并运行它
expected to fail as we haven't
预计会失败，因为我们没有
implemented the functionality yet moving
实现了功能但仍在发展
back to the implementation in the spirit
回到实施精神
of test-driven development we can do the
测试驱动的开发，我们可以做到
simplest change that will make the test
进行测试的最简单的更改
pass
通过
now that we've made these changes we can
现在我们已经进行了这些更改，我们可以
see the gutter is a different color for
看到装订线是一种不同的颜色
the lines we've changed we can also
我们改变的路线我们也可以
click on the gutter and see more useful
点击装订线，看到更多有用的
features we can for example undo this
我们可以例如取消此功能
specific change if we need to
如果需要，可以进行具体更改
we can open the changes in a separate de
我们可以在单独的de中打开更改
few and we can copy the original code
很少，我们可以复制原始代码
that we've now overwritten
现在我们已经覆盖了
let's open the version control window we
让我们打开版本控制窗口
can get to it from the tool windows
可以从工具窗口进入
button in the bottom left or we can use
左下角的按钮，或者我们可以使用
Alt + 9 or command + 9 to open it here
Alt + 9或Command + 9在此处打开
the default change list shows a list of
默认更改列表显示以下列表
all the files we've changed and we can
我们已更改的所有文件，我们可以
see any new files that haven't been
查看尚未的任何新文件
added to version control yet we can
添加到版本控制中，但我们可以
commit these changes by right-clicking
通过右键单击提交这些更改
and selecting commit or we can use ctrl
并选择提交，或者我们可以使用ctrl
K or command key to open the commit
K或Command键打开提交
dialog the commit dialog shows the files
对话框提交对话框显示文件
we've changed and any new files we've
我们已经更改，并且我们有任何新文件
created that we might want to add
创建了我们可能想要添加的
we can enable a dip view of the files
我们可以启用文件的倾斜视图
that have changed at the bottom and we
底部发生了变化，我们
can cycle through all the changes to see
可以循环浏览所有更改以查看
if they're okay we can enter a commit
如果他们还可以，我们可以输入一次提交
message and IntelliJ IDEA will even
消息和IntelliJ IDEA甚至
check our spelling here
在这里检查我们的拼写
on the right there are a number of
在右边有一些
automatic steps that can be applied
可以应用的自动步骤
before we commit we can reformat or
在我们提交之前，我们可以重新格式化或
rearrange our code we can optimize the
重新排列我们的代码，我们可以优化
imports which I'm going to choose to do
我要选择做的进口
we can analyze the code for potential
我们可以分析代码的潜力
problems and check if any to-do items
问题并检查是否有待办事项
should have been addressed I'm going to
应该已经解决了，我要去
turn both of these off as I want to make
我想把这两个都关掉
the commit process as quick as possible
提交过程尽可能快
we can also automatically clean up
我们也可以自动清理
problems that have been identified by
被发现的问题
our inspections and update any copyright
我们的检查并更新任何版权
text now it can commit all our changes
现在发送文本，它可以提交我们的所有更改
we can see there are no longer any
我们可以看到不再有
changed files in the default change list
默认更改列表中的已更改文件
but we do have one on version file if we
但是如果我们确实在版本文件上有一个
add this file to our git ignore file
将此文件添加到我们的git ignore文件中
will see that this no longer appears in
将会看到它不再出现在
our local changes view and we won't be
我们的本地变更视图，我们不会
prompted to add it to get
提示将其添加以获取
another useful feature is the ability to
另一个有用的功能是
see the get history for a specific file
查看特定文件的获取历史记录
we can see the dip for each revision and
我们可以看到每个修订的底线，
we can even compare any revision with
我们甚至可以将任何修订与
the current version probably the most
当前版本可能是最
useful view for working with version
使用版本的有用视图
control systems is the log view here you
控制系统是您的日志视图
can see all the revisions the author and
可以看到作者和所有的修订
the dates of these revisions the files
这些修订的日期文件
that make up a revision and see a diff
组成修订并看到差异
for that file
对于那个文件
in our case we can see that our master
就我们而言，我们可以看到我们的主人
branch is two commits ahead of the
分支是前面的两个提交
remote master branch we want to push
我们要推送的远程主分支
those changes to the remote
那些更改到遥控器
we can do this either via the push menu
我们可以通过推菜单来做到这一点
item or using shift control K or shift
项目或使用变速控制K或变速
command K
命令K
in the push dialog we can select a
在推送对话框中，我们可以选择一个
remote to push to in our case we only
远程推送到我们的情况下，我们只
have one so we'll leave that as it is we
有一个，所以我们将其保留原样
can also optionally push to a different
也可以选择推送到其他
branch again we'll leave this as master
再次分支，我们将其保留为主
it's also possible to force a push but
也可以强行推动，但
we're on the master branch and this
我们在master分支上
branch is protected from force push by
保护分支不受强制推动
default now we push our changes and we
现在默认，我们推送更改，我们
can see this was successful let's look
可以看到这是成功的，让我们来看看
at slightly more advanced features the
在稍微高级的功能上
branches menu shows us which branch
分支菜单向我们显示哪个分支
we're on and provides us with helpful
我们正在为您提供帮助
working with branches we can create a
与分支机构合作，我们可以创建一个
new branch from here if we want to or we
如果需要，可以从这里创建新分支
can select any commit in the log view
可以在日志视图中选择任何提交
and when we right-click and select new
当我们右键单击并选择新
branch we can create a branch of that
分支，我们可以创建一个分支
revision by default IntelliJ IDEA will
默认情况下，IntelliJ IDEA将进行修订
check out that new branch so if you
签出新的分支，所以如果你
don't want to be working on the new
不想在新的
branch you need to uncheck this box now
分支，您现在需要取消选中此框
we've created and checked out our new
我们已经创建并签出了新的
branch we can work on some new features
分支，我们可以开发一些新功能
on this branch we're going to implement
在这个分支上，我们将要实施
the vertices feature for circles on this
圆形的顶点特征
branch following the same process as we
按照与我们相同的过程进行分支
did for squares we run the test make the
做正方形，我们进行测试，使
change and rerun the test
更改并重新运行测试
let's explore some other features of the
让我们探讨一下
commit dialog we can reuse an old commit
提交对话框，我们可以重用旧的提交
message and edit it if we wish we could
消息并编辑它，如果我们希望可以的话
also commit and push our changes in one
还承诺并推动我们的改变
action we can do this using the keyboard
动作，我们可以使用键盘来做到这一点
shortcut ctrl Alt key or alt command + K
快捷键ctrl Alt键或alt命令+ K
IntelliJ IDEA shows us this will create
IntelliJ IDEA向我们展示了这一点
a new branch on our remote
遥控器上的新分支
when this is done our log view shows the
完成此操作后，我们的日志视图将显示
new branch and the commits on all our
新分支和我们所有的提交
branches we can switch back to the
分支，我们可以切换回
master branch by right-clicking on the
右键点击主分支
branch name selecting the master branch
分支名称选择主分支
menu item and clicking on checkout now
菜单项，然后单击立即结帐
we can continue making changes to
我们可以继续进行更改
support our square functionality with a
通过以下方式支持我们的正方形功能
passing test we commit these changes to
通过测试，我们将这些更改提交给
our branch which is master and when we
我们的分支是主人，当我们
view the log we can see the master
查看日志，我们可以看到大师
branch is updated with our new commit we
分支使用我们的新提交更新
can see in the log view that there are
可以在日志视图中看到
commits on two branches master and
提交到两个分支master和
circle changes at this time if we now
如果现在我们现在圈子变化
want to merge our circle changes we can
想要合并我们的圈子更改，我们可以
right click on the branch we want to
右键单击我们想要的分支
merge making sure were on the correct
合并确保正确
branch and select merge into current
分支并选择合并到当前
IntelliJ IDEA performs the merge and
IntelliJ IDEA执行合并和
lets us know that we don't need the
让我们知道我们不需要
circle changes branch anymore and offers
圈子不再更改分支并提供
to delete it when we delete this branch
删除该分支时将其删除
we can also delete the remote circle
我们也可以删除远程圈子
changes branch so IntelliJ IDEA makes it
更改分支，以便IntelliJ IDEA实现
easy for us to clean up unnecessary
方便我们清理不必要的东西
branches as we go
分支随着我们走
now we've made a number of changes to
现在我们对
our square class we can see another nice
我们的班级，我们可以看到另一个好地方
feature in IntelliJ IDEA for any file in
IntelliJ IDEA中的功能针对其中的任何文件
version control we can right click in
版本控制，我们可以右键单击
the gutter and select annotate this
装订线并选择对此进行注释
shows the author and the date of the
显示作者和日期
last change for every line in the file
文件中每一行的最后更改
hovering over one of these will show
将鼠标悬停在其中之一上将显示
more information including the commit
更多信息，包括提交
message double clicking will show all
消息双击将显示全部
the files changed during that commit
在提交期间更改的文件
right click and select annotate again to
右键单击并再次选择注释
turn off annotations as our last step
关闭注释，这是我们的最后一步
let's push all the changes to master to
让我们将所有更改推送到主
the remote and the log view shows
远程和日志视图显示
everything is now up to date you can see
现在一切都保持最新状态，您可以看到
IntelliJ is integration with version
IntelliJ与版本集成
control systems like git is designed to
像git这样的控制系统旨在
make it easy for developers to work
使开发人员易于工作
effectively with source control thanks
有效地进行源代码控制谢谢
for watching
观看
you
您